So you were helping her
find her lost brother?
Yes, she hired me for it.
She said they were separated
when they were very young.
And you got them happily reunited?!
Yes.
That's great!
Wait. But then...
What was with the ring?
It was a memento from their parents,
who died when they were children.
The brother got their mother's ring.
The sister got their father's tie pin.
They kept them as proof
that they were siblings.
Dammit. That's wholesome.
May I ask why you two were tailing me?
Oh, you saw us?
I told you he would!
I'm so sorry we interrupted your work!
Oh, it's fine.
I assumed you were shadowing me to see
if I was a worthy partner
for Shizuka-san, so...
Wait, is he watching me?
I have to get this job done right
so he sees I'm a hard worker!
I was pretty nervous but...
did I get it wrong?
Oh, shut up.
Oh, s-sorry.
Point is, if you ever do
anything to hurt my sister,
I'll bash you with my bat, so be ready.
That bat is plastic, isn't it?
You have a bat? What?!
You're not staying with me tonight?
I'll stay at a net cafe tonight
and make my way home tomorrow.
But why?!
Would you both like to stay at my place?
You sure?
Yes, I have space for three.
A-Are you sure, Akira-san?
Futa-san, you don't have
to accommodate us.
Nah, it's cool.
Ah. I see.
Next time, maybe.
By all means!
Oh, Fu-kun...
Now, now.
You've always been like this!
If this guy marries my sister...
We'll basically be family, right?
But at least let me spot you
a proper hotel...
I don't know much about him
besides the detective stuff.
Akira-san! You don't have to
play the SD with Fu-kun!
I don't wanna be family with
a guy whose expressions I can't even read.
What? I didn't mean to...
But that stuff doesn't matter to sis.
She acts normal even around him.
You're SDing all over the place!
Later.
Tonome-san.
You better look after my sister.
I-I will.
Good morning. I made breakfast. You can
heat it up in the microwave and eat it.
It's from Akira-san.
Let's find out what he made me...
French toast, courtesy of Akira-san!
It's not too sweet, either!
Akira-san had to go to work early,
but we have tomorrow off!
I know!
I believe we have... carrots!
And...
Potatoes, right?
And the roux should be...
I'm back.
Welcome back!
Akira-san?
You're not mad at me for cooking
while you were gone, right?!
It's just...
I never thought I'd be
coming home to your cooking...
I'm so happy!
Well, you made breakfast for me, too...
It matters to me that
you made yourself at home.
It's like we're really married, right?
I'm blushing so hard!
How long is every little thing
going to tickle me like this?!
Oh, speaking of...
I got an email from my rental agency.
They say my lease is up for renewal soon.
Do you think, maybe...
Yes, we'd better hurry.
We've been so cautious about selecting
a property, we haven't gotten it done.
AT MOST A 10 MINUTE WALK FROM THE STATION - SAFE AREA
CLOSE ENOUGH TO WORK - NEAR A CONVENIENCE STORE
We never found anything
that fit all our wants, yeah...
But I've loved the nights
we've spent together.
Though my apartment's so small,
we've mostly spent them at yours...
Would you rather put off getting
a place of our own?
No, I definitely want to
get a place of our own!
But I've gotten so used to this place,
the idea of shifting to a new environment
feels both exciting and sad, all at once.
Hey...
Would you just like to move in here?
I didn't know that was an option!
Then you won't have to
get used to a new place.
True!
Then let's start packing up
your things and move them here!
Okay!
That was easy, wasn't it?!
It was an unexpected blind spot.
Hey, you're moving in with Tonome?
That's such a big moment!
Huge, indeed!
We're going through
the process of moving things now!
If you need any heavy lifting,
give me a call!
I can carry your stuff to Tonome's house
without breaking a sweat!
You mean it?!
So cool!
Easy as pie!
So strong!
I can have it done in an hour!
Hey, Tonome.
What is it?
So fast!
The girls are acting like we're
in the Stone Age out there,
It's easier than breathing!
but you wanna use our van to move?
I'd love that!
Welcome to the Elf Garden!
I'd like some black tea for a gift.
Sure thing! I recommend one of these!
By the way, what's up with your wife?
Haven't seen her in a while.
Why'd it get dark?
She didn't abandon me.
K-Karma-san?!
You'll be okay!
She's coming back, right?!
So bright!
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Hey, I can handle the heavy lifting!
Put that down!
Th-Thanks.
But stand back first.
Stand back?
A little more!
More!
There, that'll do it.
My curse shouldn't affect you
from that distance!
I've received blessings from all
the white elves in the elf forest!
One little dark elf curse
won't do squat to hurt me,
so shut up and apply that
stretch mark cream to my belly!
B-But...
You're still on that?!
You think the power
of white elves can't—
Light? Light?!
Contractions?!
Yeah. Started all of a sudden.
So the baby's coming soon?
But there's still a little
while until her due date.
So I got freaked out
and panicked a little.
Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
Light! Baby!
Don't die!
Calm down!
Call my father and the hospital now!
And get my overnight bag!
R-Right!
Here.
Karma. I didn't tell you this, but...
It's actually...
Twins?!
Yes.
She said she wanted to
keep it secret as a surprise.
Are you not actually happy about that?
Oh, a cup fell off the shelf.
It's been like this since
Light went to the hospital.
I'm so nervous about the babies arriving
safely, my curses keep leaking out.
Will the delivery be difficult?
No.
Light's family has been at the hospital,
preparing for the birth.
I think that should all be fine.
Her whole family is there?
White elves start the birthing
process by being bathed in blessings.
But...
If my curses did anything
to harm Light or the babies...
Karma-san, when you
invited us out here...
Were you trying
to pass your curse on to us?
Busted?!
Let's leave here at once, Shizuka-san.
Wait, please!
I'm so worried I can't take it anymore!
I understand that you're upset,
but can't you vent your curse
power like you did before?
My fear is outpacing what I can vent!
Can't I share the burden with you?!
I won't allow you
to drag Shizuka-san into this!
What's wrong with passing
my curses on to people?!
I wouldn't know where to begin!
Akira-san!
It's twins, and it's her first pregnancy.
I think we should try
to comfort him as much as possible.
Shizuka-san?
Can't we stay with him
just a little while?
Shizuka-chan's so nice!
But you'll be in danger if anything
else falls, so remain beside me.
Y-Yes!
Yes!
And Karma-san will maintain
a respectful distance.
What just happened? Are you all right?!
How scary!
Where did that washbasin come from?!
I managed to convince
Shizuka-san to go home, but...
Snuggle snuggle snuggle snuggle!
Why are you clinging to me?!
Interesting question!
You've been like this the whole time.
Wanna go to your place?
I'll pick us up something
at the convenience store!
You're coming to my place?!
Don't be a shy guy!
Hang on, brb!
Don't—
Seriously, how?!
Karma-san isn't even here!
Looks like I've granted you
some of my curse, Tonome-chan!
What?! But I don't feel any different...
Worked faster than I thought!
You just passed your curse on to me!
Take it off, please!
That's not happening, bro!
I'm a cursed dark elf, remember?!
Why are you acting proud of that?!
How long is this supposed to last?!
Well, duh! Until my fears go away!
Which means until the babies are born!
Hey, it's the hospital!
They say I can talk to her!
Oh, it's Light-san?
Your babies will be here soon.
You must be excited to meet them.
Y-Yeah...
L-Later.
That's right. I'll meet them soon.
And yet...
I've got to stop.
Thinking just makes me more scared...
LIGHT
LIME VIDEO CALL
Hello?
Karma!
Light! You okay?
I'm fine.
They've given me all
the blessings I need for now.
Are you coming soon?
Of co—
I can't.
I really can't be there.
I can't afford to curse the babies.
What are you talking about?
Karma, please!
I can't do it!
Even if you say it's fine, if...
if I come by and something really happens
to you and the babies...
I...
Are you crying?
I'm sorry! I'm so useless...
and helpless...
Listen to me!
I don't need you to do anything.
I just want you here!
Karma. Come and be with me!
Are you crying too?
It's just... It's just...
I'm also super nervous, and the babies
are waiting for you, stupid!
Get over yourself and
come over here now!
I'm sorry.
I'm coming.
I know I said I wouldn't run away.
Shizuka-san.
Kikira-san said he'd be by this evening.
Roger that!
Shizuka-san,
I should put these old dishes
in the trash pick-up spot, right?
Thank you!
A-Are you all right?
Stay back! It's not safe!
Ow!
It just ripped through all
the packing tape at once?
I think it's Karma-san's curse in action.
He said he'd transferred
some of his curse to me.
It means bad things will happen
even when he's not in the room.
It apparently just causes
small misfortunes, though.
If only I'd stuck around longer...
Well, I didn't want you
to get hit by it, too...
I want to protect you, Akira-san!
Shizuka-san...
Seriously, why washbasins?!
I'm sorry!
A-Akira-san!
I'm sorry. I came to help, and yet...
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't asked to stay
with Karma-san in the first place...
And then you tried to help me move
and ended up having a miserable time...
Seriously, it's just the curse...
You dropped the dishes and got hurt...
If you hadn't come to help me,
the curse's effects might
not have been so bad!
Akira-san, why don't you
go home and take it easy?
They're my things, after all.
I can work on the packing
until Kikira-san comes!
Shizuka-san. Don't say something so sad.
I've been working despite the problems
because I want you by my side.
Really?
Really.
You're not getting rid
of me that easily.
I-I wasn't trying to get rid of you!
Besides...
I don't want Karma-san's curse
to affect our relationship.
That's also fair.
I know!
The curse won't move
from you to me, right?
Right.
Then, since I'm not
affected by the curse,
if I lie on top of you,
things shouldn't fall on you, right?!
What?
If I may!
Take that, you stupid curse!
You're helpless in the face of this!
Nothing's happening. I think it's worked!
Shizuka-san, can't breathe...
Do excuse me!
N-No problem.
KARMA-SAN
LIME VIDEO CALL
Hello? Yes?
Tonome-chan! My babies! My twins!
They're here!
Congratulations!
Your curses didn't hurt anything?
Everyone's doing just fine!
Well, that's great to hear.
I'm so glad I got to be with Light
and meet the babies.
If not for you,
the curse probably would have
crushed me before I made it.
You really are the guy
to have around in a pinch!
I'd rather not be, though...
Well, I'm just glad everyone's fine.
My curse should have
lost effect by now, too!
Oh, that explains that.
It may have been gone for a while.
I guess covering you
didn't do much, but...
I'm glad it's gone.
I'm glad that you
were willing to protect me.
Hey, I'm here.
Thanks for coming.
We had a little trouble,
so packing's fallen behind, but...
No problem. I assumed
we'd be helping out.
Hey there!
Madaraito-san!
Daichi told us everything!
The more hands the better, right?
You're all here! Thank you so much!
Where are the boxes?
I'll carry out whatever's ready now.
They'll get it done, right?
Thank you for all your help!
Later!
See ya!
Looks like we got it all here.
They really had everything
running smoothly, right?
Yes.
Let's take our time
getting things unpacked.
That's right... We never got
to eat, did we?
Yes.
How about we order pizza
and have a moving party?
Pizza!
Good moving!
Yeah!
Our life together begins, right?
Yes.
Oh, that's right.
I wanted to give you something.
What could it be now?
Could it be...
A ring?!
We've met each other's parents, too...
Or am I just leaping
to conclusions again?!
Please hold out your left hand.
Left hand?!
Is it really...?
What is this?
The key.
It's our place now, after all.
Yours and mine?!
It turned out to be
a bit of a rehearsal, too,
but I had an extra key made earlier...
Akira-san!
Right.
Akira-san...
I love you!
A-And...
Yes?
I wanna use our key,
so let's go somewhere!
Good idea.
How about getting some
dessert from the store?
Yes!
An outing and dessert for our big day!
What should we get?
Good question.
They have a lot of great
desserts these days!
What are you getting?
EPISODE 12: A BIG MOMENT
THE END
A chocolate banana crepe.